原创翻译  双语字幕
我叫约翰·迪根  来自哥谭
My name is John Deegan, and I'm from Gotham,
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
那是一座急需英雄的城市
a city in grave need of heroes.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
作为阿卡姆疯人院的一名医生
As a doctor at Arkham Asylum,
我尽自己的责任
I did my part
保护这座城市不受精神病犯罪者的伤害
by protecting this city from the criminally insane.
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
这个世界不理解我的方法
The world didn't understand my methods,
校对     肉松  饿得慌
于是我暗中工作  直到有一天
so I worked in secret until, one day,
一个宇宙人意识到了我的潜力
when a cosmic being recognized my potential
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
让我有机会成为更伟大的存在
and gave me the chance to be something greater.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
更伟大的人
Someone greater.
现在  我是超人
Now, I am Superman.
总监     你是不是饿得慌
《绿箭》及《闪电侠》前情提要...
Previously on Arrow and Flash...
整个世界认为
The world thinks
你是奥利弗·奎恩  而我是巴里·艾伦
that you're Oliver Queen and that I'm Barry Allen,
我非常想知道这是为什么
and I would really like to know why.
我们接下来怎么办
So what's our next move?
我们去哥谭市
We're going to Gotham City.
你是谁  你为什么要帮我们
Who are you and why are you helping us?
凯恩  凯特·凯恩
Kane. Kate Kane.
他自称为监视者
He calls himself the Monitor.
他在多元宇宙释放了《命运之书》
He's been unleashing the Book of Destiny
来考验不同的地球
across the multiverse to test different Earths.
危机迫在眉睫  有个人要来了
A crisis is imminent. Someone is coming.
一个远比我强大的人
Someone far, far more powerful than myself.
我想做好准备
I mean to prepare.
扳机双子
银行抢劫嫌疑犯
通缉
又来了  他重写现实了
He did it again. He rewrote reality.
超人
Superman!
无论你们跑到哪里  我都能找到你们
There's no place you can run where I can't find you.
结束了
It's over.
你说什么呢
What're you talking about?
克拉克  是我们啊  巴里和奥利弗
Clark, it's us. Barry and Oliver.
我知道你们是谁
Oh, I know who you are.
你们还没搞清楚我是谁
Your confusion lies with me.
迪根
Deegan.
监视者把书还给你了吗
The Monitor gave you the book back?
还告诉了我真正的使用方法
And showed me how to really use it.
你不能把自己写成英雄
You can't just write yourself as a hero.
那样不行
It doesn't work that way.
有什么不行
Doesn't it, though?
你们被闪电击中
You were struck by lightning.
而更高权力给了我那本书
I was given the book by a higher power.
两者都是偶然的随机事件
Both random acts of chance.
但这个
But this,
这是我的命运
this is my destiny.
比你成为闪电侠的命运更加重要
So much more than becoming the Flash was ever yours.
人们不会因为某种境遇而成为英雄
People don't become heroes because of circumstance.
而是无论境遇如何  都会成为英雄
They become heroes in spite of circumstance.
你只是个廉价的山寨货
You're just a cheap knockoff.
我一点都不廉价
Oh, I'm anything but cheap.
你们可以看看我还做了哪些有趣的改变
And just wait till you see what other fun changes I've made.
对你们的家人  朋友
To your family, your friends.
你们再也没有安全的港湾
There is no safe harbor for you.
这不再是你们的世界  而是我的
This is no longer your world. It's mine!
我有个主意
I have an idea.
白痴  我刀枪不入
Idiot, I'm bulletproof.
我知道
I know.
你想成为地球的英雄吗
You wanna be Earth's hero?
要么救下那些孩子  要么阻止我们
Save the children or stop us.
你来选  超人
Your choice, Superman.
超 女
第四季 第九集
异    世    界
第三篇
做坏事让我感觉很糟糕  老兄
Being bad makes me feel bad, man.
那台吊车本来就不会砸到人
The crane gag was harmless.
它会倒在空荡荡的停车场上
It would've landed in an empty parking lot.
但我还是感觉很糟糕
Still, man. I don't know.
故意做那种事情
Just doing something like that on purpose,
让我想吐  我...
I think I'm gonna puke. I'm...
我没事  我没事
No, I'm okay, I'm okay.
我们要搞清楚现实到底发生了多大的变化
We need to find out how extensive this reality-change is,
我们得找点旁门左道  走吧
and we need to get off the streets. Come on.
我什么都吐不出来
I can't get anything coming up. I can't...
等等  我有个计划
Wait up. I have a plan.
-祝贺你  先生  -你轻松接住了那台吊车
- Congratulations, sir. -The way you caught that crane,
就好像它轻如鸿毛
like it weighed nothing.
太厉害了
Very, very impressive.
逃犯逃走了
The fugitives escaped!
先生  我们相信你一定会把他们绳之以法
Sir, we are quite sure you will bring them back to justice.
没有人能逃出超人的掌心
No one can escape Superman.
你真这么认为吗
You really think so?
先生  你比他们强大多了
Sir, you are far too powerful.
你说得对  你说得对
Ah, you're right. You're right.
先生  管道出问题了
Sir, the pipeline.
肯定是一号囚犯搞的鬼  她整个上午都在制造噪音
Must be subject one. She's been making noise all morning.
-交给我处理  -不
-I'll handle this. -No!
你继续追踪艾伦和奎恩  我来处理她
You stay on Allen and Queen. I'll handle her.
我认识佩戴这个符号的真正男子汉
I know the real man who wears that glyph.
不是你
It's not you.
你不是超人
You're not Superman.
然而  我成为了曾经的你
And yet, I am all that you once were.
没有冒犯巴里·艾伦的意思
No offense to Barry Allen,
但是作为英雄  你...
but as a hero, you...
你远远不止比子弹还快那么简单
You are so much more than just faster than a speeding bullet.
所以你模仿我的能力和家徽
So, you're imitating my powers and my family crest,
却不模仿我的性别
but not my gender?
害怕做个女人吗
Too afraid to be a woman?
我什么都不怕
Oh, I'm not afraid of anything.
《命运之书》向我揭示了
The Book of Destiny revealed to me
关于巴里·艾伦和奥利弗·奎恩的一切
all there is to know about Barry Allen and Oliver Queen,
但你和这个钢铁之躯
but for you and this Man of Steel,
却毫无记载
there was nothing.
除了你在中城对战过的机器人什么都没有
Nothing but the android you fought in Central City. It's...
就像你在这个世界不存在一样
It's as if you don't exist in this world.
所以你把我关起来  抑制我的能力
That's why you locked me up and dampened my powers.
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are.
我不知道你是如何来到这里的
I don't know how you got here,
但那些都不重要  因为现在我就是你
but none of that matters because I am now you.
全新且更好的你
New and improved.
而你再也别想重见天日了
And you will never see the light of day again.
我会阻止你
I'm gonna stop you.
没什么可阻止的
There's nothing to stop.
我就是这个地球需要的英雄
I am the hero this planet needs.
谢谢你  丹弗斯特工
Thank you, Agent Danvers.
这些牢房时刻都有人巡逻
These cells are patrolled 24/7,
所以不要耍小聪明
so don't get any bright ideas,
否则你的下场会非常痛苦
or you will end up hurting in a very painful way.
你只有进了棺材才能离开这里
The only way out of here for you is in a casket.
等等  艾丽克斯
Wait! Alex.
你以为你认识那个特工
Oh, you think you know that agent.
我扰乱了这个地球上每个人的现实
You see, I scrambled the reality of everyone on this Earth.
每个人都不是原本的样子
No one is who they were.
但我想即使是重写命运
But I guess even rewritten destiny
也有办法开开玩笑
has a way of playing jokes.
你乖乖做个好囚犯
You be a good prisoner,
不然我就杀了她
or I kill her.
-你是个怪物  -不
- You're a monster. - No.
我是超人
I'm Superman.
好  我们找到西斯科  闯进地球三十八
Okay, we get Cisco, breach to Earth-38,
找到真的超人
find real Superman.
计划是这样的
That's the plan.
只要这个西斯科肯帮我们
As long as this Cisco's willing to help us.
上个改写现实里的西斯科没帮上什么忙
The last alternate version of Cisco I met was not super-helpful.
谁知道这次他会被改写成什么样
Who knows how he's been rewritten this time?
先生们
Gentlemen.
我们是时候谈谈你们的命运了
It's time we talked about your destiny.
我必须承认
I must confess,
你们激起了我的兴趣
my interest is piqued.
你们既没有力量也没有能力
You possess neither power nor abilities,
却仍设法用智慧胜过了对手
yet still managed to outwit an opponent
一个拥有超能力的超级人类
with the powers of a super man.
只用一个词就行  "超人"
It's just one word, "Superman."
你这是什么意思
What is this?
假如你要考验我们  就不要打断我们
If you're testing us, then let us get back to it.
奥利弗·奎恩
Oliver Queen,
一个将自己的狂妄与愤怒称为力量的男人
a man who channels his hubris and anger and calls it strength.
你真的那么求死心切吗
Are you truly that eager to die?
不  不是心切
No. Not eager.
但愿意送死
But willing.
准备好送死
Ready to.
很好
Good.
这个宇宙或许还有希望
There might be hope for this universe yet.
假如你想鼓励我们  效果实在不怎么样
If that's supposed to be a pep talk, I've had better.
单靠自我牺牲不会让你通过这次试炼
Self-sacrifice alone will not see you through this trial.
只有认清真正的自己才能幸存
Survival will only be found by knowing your true self,
否则这世界将会毁灭
or this world will be doomed,
像其他世界一样
like all the others.
好了  够了
Okay, that's enough.
他的话可真让人悲观啊
Well, that was very glass-half-empty.
我们得找到西斯科
We need to find Cisco.
假如我们好人都变成了坏人
Okay, well, if us good guys are bad guys,
那就有理由认为我们的好人朋友也变成了坏人
stands to reason that our good-guy friend is now a bad guy.
当然  你是中城警局的
Sure. You're CCPD.
这座城市的罪犯都在哪出没
Where do criminals hang out in this city?
-他们好像都很怕我们  -顺其自然吧
- Are they all afraid of us? - Go with it.
-这主意真糟糕  -你一直这么说
- This is a terrible idea. - You keep saying that.
可我们还是到这来了
And yet, here we are anyway.
我们需要盟友和资源
We need allies and resources.
我的天  是扳机双子
Oh, my God, the Trigger Twins.
抱歉  我是你们犯罪史的大粉丝
Sorry, I'm just a huge fan of your criminal history.
你们是我的英雄
You guys are my heroes.
不是英雄  是传奇
Well, not heroes. Legends.
你们想要什么
Can I get you guys something?
很显然  我们需要盟友和资源
Apparently, we need allies and resources.
我们在找西斯科·雷蒙
We're looking for Cisco Ramon.
你是指老大
You mean the boss?
是啊
Sure.
勉强算有点用吧
Well, that's not nothing.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
我来自其他地球
I'm not from this Earth.
我所在的地球上  我们是姐妹
Where I come from, we're sisters.
你
You?
你是最卑劣的那一个
You are as despicable as they come.
传说中你所做过的那些邪恶之事...
I mean, the stories of all the twisted things that you've done...
艾丽克斯  我知道有些事在你看来是一种模样
Alex, I know things look one way to you,
我在你眼中是一种模样
that I look one way to you,
但这不是现实
but the way things are, it's not real.
不是原本的现实
Not really real.
如果你能让我解释  我可以告诉你...
And if you just let me explain, I can tell you--
你很危险  而且你显然疯了
You are dangerous, and you are clearly crazy,
我还有工作要做
and I have work to do.
不要  等等  听我解释
No, wait. Wait, just let me explain.
我可以把一切都告诉你
I can tell you everything.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
去跟我的助理定时间
Make an appointment with my assistant.
我大概在"去你们的"左右有时间
I should have an opening around "Go screw yourself."
西斯科  我们需要你的帮助
Cisco, we need your help.
听着
Listen.
我不知道你以为自己是谁
I don't know who you think you are.
但是在这里  人们叫我雷蒙先生
But around here, people call me Mr. Ramon.
你那边有麻烦了吗  雷蒙先生
You got a problem there, Mr. Ramon?
听见了吧
Case in point.
吉米  我觉得这两位宠物店男孩
Jimmy, I think the Pet Shop Boys here
需要知道一下这里的规矩
need an education in how things work around here.
这不成问题
I don't think that should be a problem.
他们叫我超人最坏的伙伴不是没缘由的
They don't call me Superman's worst pal for nothing.
听着  我们不想惹麻烦
Look, we don't want any trouble.
我们只是想向雷蒙先生做个商业提议
We just have a business proposal for Mr. Ramon.
商业提议  我看算了吧
Business proposal. I'm gonna pass.
我喜欢看我的手下
You see, I like watching my people
痛扁其他人  所以...
put a beating on other people. So...
所以  我们在这点上很像
So, I guess we got that in common.
我们能应付  对吧
We've got this, right?
完全能
Totally.
现在要求跟你们自拍合适吗
Is now an okay time to ask for a selfie?
停  停  停
Stop. Stop. Stop.
吉米  你想什么呢
Jimmy, what are you thinking?
你是要在这里杀了他们吗
What, are you gonna kill 'em here, now?
盖瑞还在清理你上一次留下的烂摊子
Gary's still cleaning up from the last mess you made,
发条橙
Clockwork Orange.
在外边小巷里解决他们
Do 'em out in the alley.
好了  来吧  咱们走
All right, come on. Let's go.
等等  我认识你兄弟  丹堤
Wait, wait! I knew your brother. Dante!
停  等一下
Stop. Hold up.
你怎么会认识丹堤
How do you know Dante?
说来话长
It's a long story.
如果他在这里  他会告诉你听我们的提议
If he were here, he'd tell you to listen to our proposal.
我们的提议是什么
What's our proposal?
你想不想除掉超人
How'd you like to get rid of Superman?
好吧  我在睡觉前
All right, I've got ledgers to keep
还有一大堆的帐要记
and miles to go before I sleep,
所以快点说
so talk fast.
好  但首先  我们要知道你会不会震波
Right. But first, we need to know if you can vibe.
-我会不会震波  -传送
- Can I vibe? - Teleport.
打开缺口  你还能做到吧
Open a breach. You can still do that, right?
明知故问
Rhetorical question.
不然你以为我是怎么进入那些银行金库的
How do you think I got into all those bank vaults?
但是你们
But you,
你们不知道这一点
you didn't know that.
你们来到这里  却不知道
You came in here not knowing
我能不能做到你认为我能做到的事
if I could do what you thought I could do.
这可很危险
That's very risky.
我们有些绝望
We're kind of desperate.
我越来越不想跟你们做生意了
Please keep giving me more reasons to not do business with you.
听着  利用这种能力
All right, listen. You could use your powers
你能做到的远不止闯入金库那么简单
for so much more than breaking into bank vaults.
接着说除掉超级混蛋那件事
Go back to the part about taking down Super-dick.
我只想听那一部分
That's the part I wanna hear.
我们会说到那件事的
We're gonna get to that.
现在  我可以教你怎么运用你的能力
For now, I could teach you how to use your powers
来传送到不同的地球上
to get to a whole different Earth.
不同的地球
A whole different Earth.
继续说
Tell me more.
丹弗斯
Danvers.
老大出去了
The big guy is out,
追查双子的线索
chasing down a lead on the Twins.
迪格尔可以在楼上监视那些混球
You know, Diggle can monitor these sorry sacks from upstairs.
-你下班吧  -没事的
- Why don't you take the night off? - It's okay.
我还有些工作要做
I still have some work to do.
这是几个星期来第三次
You know, that's the third time in just as many weeks
我叫你回家  你却拒绝了我
I've told you to go home, and you've turned me down.
你撅着小嘴真的很影响我的心情
You know, this sorry little pout's really bringing me down.
你为什么不想回家呢
So, why don't you want to go home?
跟男朋友吵架了吗
Boyfriend troubles?
-不是  我现在没有男朋友  -男朋友
- No. No boyfriend presently. - Boyfriend?
我以为你在和技术部的那个白痴约会
I thought you were dating that dweeb in IT.
我可不看好他
Not impressed, by the way.
好吧  我们是约了几次
Okay, it was a couple of dates.
现在他在和人事部的帕姆约会
And now he's dating Pam in HR.
小子真会挑  选人不怎么样
Boy's got a type. Also not impressed.
你要离开这个地方
You need to leave this place.
你得找点生活乐趣
You've got to get a life.
我热爱我的工作
Look, I love what I do.
工作很重要
The work is important.
你的语气和老大如出一辙
Well, now you sound like the big guy.
你我都知道我这不是在夸你
And you and I both know I don't mean that as a compliment.
虽然我相信我们为城市所作的事很伟大
Look, I'm sure the work we do for the city is great,
但是其中有一半
but half of what we do around here
只是为了支撑他的自尊心而已
is really just to prop his ego up.
什么真相  正义  美国之道
Truth, justice, and the American way?
全是为了他自己
More like me, myself, and I.
是啊
Hmm, yeah.
只工作不玩乐  不仅会让天才变蠢才
All work and no play doesn't just make a girl dull.
也会让你变得冷冰冰的
It turns your heart to ice.
相信我  那样可不好玩
And trust me, that ain't fun.
谢谢你的建议
I appreciate the offer,
但我还是想维持现状
but I'm gonna stay just the same.
随便你吧
Suit yourself.
北极  地球三十八
-谢天谢地我们到了  -嗯
- Oh, thank God we're here. - Yeah.
-只试了十七次  -是啊
- Only took 17 tries. - Yeah.
我懂了  你是个段子手
Oh, I see. You're a comedian.
你猜怎么着  你朋友是个段子手
Hey, guess what. Your friend is a comedian.
你还是巴里吗
Still Barry?
-不  我们...  -不是了
- Oh, no. We-- - No. Yeah.
你们换回来了  太好了
So it's fixed. That's great.
糟了
Oh, no.
卡拉呢
Kara?
我是雷蒙先生  我该相信他是超人吗
Mr. Ramon. Am I supposed to believe this guy is Superman?
怎么  是你们在街上随便找来的人吗
What, did you get him off the street?
你和他长得都不像
You don't even look like him.
这是什么
Hey, uh, what's this?
你真不该去碰那个东西
Yeah, you, uh... You really shouldn't touch that.
你们可以拿这个东西开个派对
Hey, you could throw a party with this thing.
买点毒品  我认识人
Get some party favors. You know, I know a guy.
一切恢复正常了
Look, everything is back to normal.
也不是一切
Well, not everything.
卡拉呢
Where's Kara?
艾丽克斯  住手
Alex, please. Stop!
他警告过你
He warned you.
我保证再也不会企图逃跑了
I promise I won't try to escape again.
你怎么知道这句话
How do you know that?
艾丽克斯·丹弗斯教我的
Alex Danvers taught it to me.
我和你说过  我不是这个地球上的人
I told you, I'm not from this Earth.
我那个地球上的艾丽克斯在六岁那年暑假
The Alex on my Earth spent a summer in Nagano
跟耶利米和伊莉莎去了日本长野县
with Jeremiah and Eliza when she was six.
她当时很想家
She was homesick.
有一天晚
And a girl from the village
村子里的一个小女孩帮她溜进一间寺庙
helped her sneak down to one of the temples one night.
她写了张纸条  放在墙缝里
She wrote a note, and she put it in a crack in the wall,
希望事情会成真
hoping it would come true.
那时我七岁  不是六岁
I was seven, not six.
村子里的那个小女孩
And that little girl in the village,
教了我那句顺口溜
she taught me that rhyme.
-意思是  -拉钩上吊不许变
- It means... - "Pinky swear."
我们第一次偷溜出去飞上天的那晚
And my Alex taught it to me
我的艾丽克斯教了我那句话
the first night we snuck out together to go flying.
我的艾丽克斯总是喜欢服务他人
My Alex was always drawn to service.
所以你如此在乎
So it's not surprising
如此关心这个世界和人们
that you care deeply, so deeply,
一点也不出奇
about this world and all the people in it.
但是在我的地球上呢
But on my Earth?
艾丽克斯不止有工作
Alex doesn't just have a job.
她还在一个跟这里类似的地方当领导
She's in charge of a place like this.
她是领导吗
She's in charge?
她是一位公正自豪的领导
She's a leader who is just and proud.
每当有人叫她做她所认为的错事时
When someone tells her to do something she knows is wrong,
她都会给他们颜色瞧
she gives them hell.
她只做正确的事
And she does what's right.
她和我不一样  她没有超能力
She doesn't have powers like I do,
但她是个英雄
but she's a hero.
我认识的这么多人中  她拥有最宽阔的胸怀
And she has the biggest heart of anyone I know,
虽然她并不总是喜欢表现出来
even though she doesn't always like to show it.
她有一些好朋友
And she has good friends.
她为自己打造了一个支持她的家庭
A real family of support that she's created for herself.
而且她不隐藏自己的真性情
And she doesn't hide who she is.
她想要有妻子
She wants a wife.
还有孩子
And kids.
她乐观地认为她可以拥有一切
She's optimistic that she could have it all.
这不是一个假设  只是时间问题
It's not an "If." It's a "When."
-听起来她很了不起  -是的
- She sounds pretty awesome. - She is.
我知道在这个星球上  我不是你妹妹
And I know I'm not your sister on this planet.
我猜我的太空舱也没在这里着陆
I guess my pod didn't land here, but...
但你还是那个人
You're still that person.
我看得出来
I can tell.
我知道
I know it.
为囚禁我们所有人  超人改写了这个现实
Superman rewrote this reality to make us all his prisoners.
我觉得你足够聪明  能看穿他的想法
I think you're smart enough to see through him.
如果我放你出来
If I were to let you out of that cell,
你会怎样  阻止他吗
you'd, what, stop him?
拉勾约定
Pinky swear.
他已经完全改变了中城
He's changed all of Central City.
甚至是整个世界
Maybe even the whole world.
大家都认为他是你  认为我们是坏人
Everybody thinks he's you, and we're bad.
我确实是坏人
I mean, I am bad.
但问题是  根本找不到卡拉
Bottom line, Kara is nowhere to be found.
如果能拿回那本书
If we get the book back,
我们应该可以重写现实
we should be able to rewrite reality again.
是吗  你打算怎么做
Yeah? And how you gonna do that?
这些冰墙后面
You got a magic pen lying around
难道有魔力笔吗
somewhere behind these ice walls?
不是笔  只是思想
It's not a pen. It's just the mind.
我以前也见过这种书
I've encountered books like this before.
作者可以用意志力
The author writes things into existence
将事物变为实体
through sheer force of will.
但是改变故事需要付出代价
But changing the story comes at a cost.
你知道书在哪里吗
Do you have any idea where the book is?
如果我是他  我会把它放在非常安全
If I were him, I'd keep it somewhere secure enough
能够关押氪星人的地方
to also hold a Kryptonian.
很简单  尖端科研实验室
Easy. S.T.A.R. Labs.
那里有严格的加密系统
That place is under lock and key.
我在那里待过
I did time there once.
-我们也待过  -对
- Hey. So did we. - We did.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我说过你可以碰我吗
Did I say you could touch me?
我说过他可以碰我吗
Did I say he could touch me?
我不记得
I missed that part.
-我得走了  -你得走了
- I have to go. - You have to go.
快看啊
Well, well, well.
我们之中有叛徒
A traitor in our midst.
其实  我之前说你可以试试
You know, when I said you should get out there
跟别人约会  丹佛斯
and start dating, Danvers,
我没想到会是这样的结果
this isn't quite what I had in mind.
我警告过你
I warned you.
不  是我骗她打开了我的牢房
No, I tricked her into opening my cell.
-我们不认识彼此  -我们认识
- We don't know each other. - Yes, we do.
她是我妹妹
She's my sister.
那你们就一起被烧死吧
Well, then you can burn together.
衣服不错
Nice suit.
博士  能跟你聊聊吗
Doctor, could I have a word, please?
我该退场了
Well, that's my cue.
走了  你们好好玩
I'm out. You ladies have fun.
-去拿书  -好
- Go get the book. -Yes!
艾丽克斯  你来了  你怎么会来这里
Alex, you're here. What are you doing here?
所有现实中都有个坏蛋  懂了
A badass in every reality. Got it.
不  没事的  他并不那么坏
No, no, no. It's okay. He's not actually bad.
-真的吗  -真的  他挺好的
- No? - No, he's fine.
-真的吗  -对  我是好人
- No-- - No, I'm good.
-抱歉  -没关系
- I'm sorry. - No, it's fine.
-我理解  没关系  -抱歉
- Badass. It's fine. - Sorry.
没关系  所以迪根  不
It's okay. Where would Deegan, um...
超人会把重要的东西放在哪里
Superman keep something valuable?
任何他很重视的东西
Anything of importance to him,
都会放在一个叫作孤独堡垒的地方
he keeps in a place called the Fortress of Solitude.
我带你们过去
I'll take you there.
我刚从孤独堡垒过来
I just came from the Fortress of Solitude.
求救  求救  我们失控了
Mayday! Mayday! We've lost control.
我控制不住  要坠机了
I can't hold it. We're going down!
异超女
Bizarro!
终于成了反派
How does it feel
你的感觉如何
to be the villain for once?
这不是什么孤独城堡  这是时间穹顶
This isn't a fortress of anything. This is the time vault.
解锁了
It's unlocked.
那么问题来了
All right, well,
应该怎么改写现实
how does one go about rewriting reality?
这个...
Well...
管道监狱的事肯定让你很虚弱
You must still be weak from The Pipeline.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我不知道迪根怎么做到的
I don't know how Deegan did it.
我能提个建议吗
Well, can I suggest that whatever it is
不管你要怎么思考  能先离开这里吗
you need to find out, we do far away from here?
-克拉克知道怎么做  -我去拿给他
- Clark knew how to do it. - I'll get this to him.
超人
Superman.
克拉克  你得打开它
Clark, we need you to open this.
挽救一切
Fix things.
他做到了
He's doing it.
是啊
Yeah.
让他合上  否则我拧断他的脖子
Make him close it, or I snap his neck.
不
No!
那你朋友就死了
Then your friend dies.
-除非我先杀了你  -奥利弗  不要
- Not if I kill you first. - Oliver, don't.
不要为了救我
Not to save me.
你不非得这样做
You don't have to do this.
你不必唤起你的黑暗面
You don't have to channel your darkness.
你可以克服它
You can overcome it.
你可以改变  可以做得更好
You can be different. You can be better.
或许就是这样
Maybe that's it.
或许这就是监视者的考验
Maybe that's the Monitor's test.
你模样真的很像他
You really look just like him.
希望只是看上去像而已
I hope that's where the resemblance ends.
所以他真的用那本书重写了整个世界吗
So he really rewrote the world with that book?
他重写了我的人生
He rewrote my life?
没错
Yeah.
有意思
It's funny.
因为我觉得我一直就是这样
Because I feel like this was always me.
但大家都是这么觉得的  对吧
But I guess everybody does, right?
这就是你
This is you.
一个愿意为正确的事情挺身而出的人
Someone who is willing to stand up for what's right.
等一切都回归正常了
I mean, after all of this goes back to normal,
你还会是这个你
that'll still be who you are.
你姐姐真是个幸运的女人
Your sister is a very lucky woman.
我是那个幸运的妹妹
I'm a lucky sister.
好了  去吧
Okay. Go.
拯救世界
Save the world.
发生什么了
What's happening?
迪根肯定又在重写现实了
Deegan must be rewriting reality again.
或者说毁灭现实
Or destroying it.
有一个办法能减慢他的速度
There might be a way to slow him down.
我们直接减慢时间
We literally slow down time.
拜托  你们过去三个小时听到的事情里
Come on, that's got to be like only the fourth most crazy thing
论疯狂程度  这只能排第四
you've heard in the past three hours.
我们怎么减慢时间  巴里
How do we slow down time, Barry?
如果超女和我以7马赫以上的速度
If Supergirl and I travel around the globe
向相反方向的方向绕行地球
in opposite directions at just over mach 7,
就能创造出足够强大的离心力
we should be able to create enough centrifugal force
减慢地球的自转
to slow the Earth's rotation.
以及地球上的一切
And everything else.
从迪根手里把书抢过来
Rip the book out of Deegan's hands,
一切就能回归正常
and everything goes back to normal.
我们可以的
We can do this.
你们两个会死的
You both die.
我打开书的时候
When I opened the book,
看见你们两个死了
I watched both of you die,
因为你们如你们所言那么做了
doing exactly what you're talking about.
如果书里这么写
If it's in the book--
那就是命运
It's destiny.
我相信克拉克
I believe Clark.
我们必须做点什么
We have to try something.
-你准备好了吗  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
卡拉
Kara.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
我有办法  你就去把书抢过来吧
I have an idea. Just get the book.
那巴里和卡拉呢
And Barry and Kara?
我们只能希望命运可以被重写
We need to hope destinies can be rewritten.
诺武
Novu!
我知道你在里面  畜生
I know you're in there, you son of a bitch!
我不怕你
I'm not afraid of you.
我不佩服你
I'm not impressed by you!
别给我玩这种游戏  出来
Stop with these games, and show yourself!
多么冲动
So much passion.
多么傲慢
And hubris.
你以为
To think,
声音够大就能给神下命令是吧
that if you just yell loud enough you can command a god.
你不是神
You're not a god.
没有名字可以用来形容我
Yet, there isn't a name for what I am,
所以我就姑且以"神"自称了
so I suppose "God" will have to do.
你的时间有限
Your time is limited.
你最好还是
I'm not sure what little
别浪费宝贵的时间向我提要求
remains is best spent making demands of me.
我已经告诉你该怎么做了
I already told you what you had to do.
我知道巴里和卡拉会发生什么
I know what happens to Barry and Kara.
所以你现在抱着一线希望  认为我能改变它
And now you're here in the faint hope I can alter it.
你刚刚说你是神
Well, you just said you were a god.
我认为你并不是
Now, I don't think you're
在考验我们是否足够强大
testing us to see if we're strong enough.
而是在考验我们是否足够正义
I think you're testing us to see if we are good enough.
而且我认为
And I don't think,
在你考验过的宇宙之中
in any of the universes you've tested,
没有任何人像我这样站在你面前
that anyone has ever stood and confronted you like this.
没错
Yes.
你是他们中的第一个
You are the first in a multitude.
我不是你需要的人
I'm not who you need!
你说如果我了解了真实的自己  就会通过考验
You said I'd pass the test if I knew my true self.
真实的我充满了黑暗
My true self is filled with darkness.
但巴里和卡拉不一样
But Barry and Kara are different.
他们给人希望
They inspire hope.
他们给人鼓励  因为他们是最好的人
They inspire people because they are the best of us.
如果你这个考验
And if this test of yours
要消除阻止这场危机最大的机会
is gonna kill our best chance at stopping this crisis,
正如神所说
well, as gods go,
你不够聪明
you're not a very smart one.
宇宙是一个错综复杂的机体
The universe is a complex piece of machinery,
必须保持平衡
and balance must be maintained.
每个改变都需要新的改变来平衡
One change requires another.
你想让我怎么保持平衡呢
How would you propose I keep the balance?
你不能胸前戴着个标志
You can't just wear that symbol on your chest
就自称英雄  迪根
and call yourself a hero, Deegan.
我们的超能力会放大自我
Our powers amplify who we are.
你使用超能力的方式
And the way you've been using yours
让我知道了你没有勇气成为英雄
tells me you don't have the mettle for this.
不  不  你错了
No. No, you're wrong.
我之前没有放开去想
I didn't think big enough.
我不会再犯那种错误了
I won't make that mistake again.
看到了吗  没人能打败我
You see? There is no defeating me!
我是这个世界的主宰者
I am the master of this world!
夸夸其谈  有点过火了  对吧
Blah, blah, blah. That's a bit much, don't you think?
宝贝
Honey?
亲爱的
Yes, dear?
一个巨型机器人
An enormous robot
拥有超人的超能力
with the powers of Superman.
真刺激
This is exciting.
谢谢你叫我来
Thank you for including me.
我会保护百姓的  结束这一切
I'll protect the civilians. Finish this.
-结束了  迪根  -不
-It's over, Deegan. - No!
我才能决定什么时候结束
I decide when the story ends!
我更喜欢蓝色的你
I liked you better in blue.
露易丝
Lois.
我就说你会接住我的
Told you you'd catch me.
巴里和卡拉
Barry and Kara,
你比我更有信心
you had more faith than I did.
我对卡拉的了解没有对巴里那么深
Well, I don't Kara as well as I know Barry,
但情况恶化的时候  他不会放慢脚步
but when things get tough, he doesn't slow down.
他会更投入  跑得更快
He digs deep and runs faster.
我的堂姐也是这样
That's my cousin to a T.
你知道我为什么对他们有信心了吧
Then you know why I had faith in them.
书里有没有说我该怎么处理这个
Does the book say anything about what I should do with this?
亚魔卓的母板
Amazo's motherboard.
所以这成了一年一度的事  是吧
So this is kind of becoming an annual thing, huh?
老天  但愿别
God, I hope not.
那是...  你在笑吗
Is that a... Are you smiling?
我有点喜欢你们了
I kind of like you guys.
别告诉任何人
Don't tell anyone.
我希望很快能再见到你们
I hope to see you all again soon.
最好不要给露易丝
Preferably without giving Lois
自己往火坑跳的新理由
another reason to dive headfirst into danger.
你跳我就跳  宝贝
I dive where you dive, babe.
西斯科  你会尽地主之谊吗
Cisco, would you do the honors?
为最爱的氪星人效劳
Anything for my favorite Kryptonian.
是的  我有一个最爱的氪星人
That's right. I have a favorite Kryptonian.
是啊  很好的选择
Yes. A good choice.
好了
Well...
下次见吧
Until next time.
和你最爱的氪星人说再见
Peace out from your favorite Kryptonian.
斯摩维尔  地球三十八
我不在的时候你做了这么多的工作
Wow, you did so much work while I was gone.
这个地方看起来太棒了
This place looks amazing.
是啊  我想确保一切为妈妈好
Yeah, well, I wanted to make sure it was all good for Ma.
布莱尼和荣恩回纳欣诺市了吗
So, uh, Brainy and J'onn went back to National City?
职责所在
Duty calls.
好吧
Well,
我希望你意识到
I hope you realize
无论是不是超查部的一员
that being a part of the DEO or not being a part of the DEO,
你都不必加入一个组织来保护世界
you don't need an organization to keep the world safe.
不管宇宙怎样
And no matter the universe,
你和艾丽克斯  总会找到办法互相支持
you and Alex, you'll find a way to have each other's backs.
是的  你说对了
Yeah, you're right.
你真的比我强太多了  卡拉
Like, you really are so much stronger than me, Kara.
每次我们在一起  我都发现了
Every time we're together, I see it.
这就是为什么
Which is why
我知道我所做的是对的
I know what I'm doing is okay.
你在做什么  克拉克
What are you doing, Clark?
你别再拐弯抹角了
You need to stop beating around the bush.
人们喜欢直接的人
People like people who are direct.
发生什么了
What is going on?
我跟你说过我们在阿尔戈很开心
I told you we had a lot of fun on Argo.
-露易丝  露易丝  -我们都是成年人了
- Lois. Lois-- - We're all adults.
你怀孕了吗
Are you having a baby?
我的天  我的天
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
是啊
Yes!
恭喜  这太棒了
Congratulations! This is so great!
我真为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
露易丝在阿尔戈最安全
And the safest place for Lois to be is on Argo.
当婴儿开始蹬脚的时候...
When the baby starts kicking...
是啊  那太可怕了
Oh, yeah, that would be awful.
所以你又要离开九个月了吗
So, you're gone another nine months?
还要更长一点
A little longer than that.
听着  这场战斗  它...
Look, this fight, it...
它让我意识到可能会失去的一切
It reminded me of everything that I could lose.
但让我放心脱掉斗篷的唯一原因
But the only reason I feel safe hanging up my cape for a while
正是你
is because of you.
这个世界有了超女后就不再需要超人
The world doesn't need Superman if it has Supergirl.
实际上这样还会更安全些
It's actually probably a bit safer.
哈佛去年的研究指出
A study out of Harvard last year
在竞争压力下  女人会比男人
said that women respond better than men
表现得更好
under competitive pressure.
我们在危机中表现得更好
We are better in a crisis.
我们更倾向于询问而不是逼问
More apt to ask questions before punching.
并不是说你不好
Not that you are not totally terrific.
至少
Bottom line,
这世界有你就安全了
the world is safe with you.
我会想念你们的
Aw. I'm gonna miss you guys.
纳欣诺市的外星人们
这个世界要是只有卡拉·丹弗斯也挺好
Honestly, the world might be fine with just Kara Danvers.
你的堂姐够好了
Your cousin ain't half bad.
克拉克  克拉克
Clark. Clark.
-什么  -烧起来了
- What? - What... It's burning.
不不不
Oh, no. No.
下次  用你的热视线吧
Next time, use your heat vision.
你说得对
Oh, you're right.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只想要一个特别的夜晚
I just wanted tonight to be special.
为什么
Why?
因为我想每晚都不一样
Because I want every night to be special.
和你一起
I mean, with you.
有很特别
But also special...
永远都是
...forever.
和你一起  我真是不会这个啊
With you... I'm so bad at this.
在堪萨斯我怎么跟你说的  直接点
What did I tell you in Kansas? Be direct.
露易丝·莱恩
Lois Lane...
-我只用说这么点吗  -是的
- That's all I had to say? - Yeah.
我喜欢直接的方式
I like this direct thing.
中城  地球一
能再次尝酒精的感觉  真是太棒了
It's nice to be able to feel the effects of alcohol again.
超高速移动有缺点也有优点
Yeah. Super speed has its pluses and its minuses.
总是很饿
Always hungry.
我老把鞋烧出洞
I was burning holes in my shoes.
你一点都不会想念这个吗
You're not gonna miss anything about it?
之前有这么些时候
There were a few times
我跑得很快
where I was running so fast,
感觉
it was like
周围的事物都停止了
things were standing still...
所有的一切都变得很清晰
Everything just felt really clear to me.
我会想念这种感觉的
I'm gonna miss that.
-闪电时间  -什么
- Flashtime. - What?
我把它叫做闪电时间
That's just what I call it.
你真的是给所有东西都要命名啊
You really have a name for everything.
有些事我也要感谢你
So I feel like I should be thanking you for something.
监视者
The Monitor.
你跟他谈过了  对吧
You talked to him, didn't you?
你让他改变了我们的命运
You got him to change our destinies somehow.
是你和卡拉改变了你们的命运  巴里
You and Kara changed your destinies, Barry,
你一直都是个英雄
by being the heroes that you always have been.
我成为过你
Hey, I've been you.
我活过  我感受过
I lived it. I felt it.
你是个好人
You're a good man.
你也是
So are you.
即使你不想让人们相信这个事实
Even if you don't want people to believe it.
我没你想象的那么好
I'm not as good as you think I am.
但是因为你
But because of you,
我会努力成为那种好人
I think I'll get there someday.
-我们要抱抱吗  -不不
- Should we hug it out? - No. No.
这次坚决不抱
And I really mean it this time.
两次  你让我抱了你两次
Twice, you've made me hug you.
-不抱了  -好吧
- No. - All right.
好吧  我认真的
Okay? I mean it.
我提议举杯
I will propose a toast.
感谢你所拥有的
To appreciating what you have,
感谢未来的时光
however long you might have it.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
我觉得你跟我们没关系了
I thought you were done with us.
想得美
Wishful thinking.
我刚从阿卡姆回来
I just came from Arkham.
告诉我你的那个疯狂医生
Tell me this deranged doctor of yours
不会成为更大的麻烦
isn't going to be a bigger problem.
迪根  为什么
Deegan? Why?
因为我听说他交了一个朋友
Because I hear he's made a friend.
别担心  医生
Don't worry, Doctor.
万事俱备
Everything is as it should be.
舞台已经建好
The stage is set.
有的世界会存续
Worlds will live.
有的世界会毁灭
Worlds will die.
整个宇宙
And the universe
届时会彻底改变
will never be the same.
2019年秋季上映
无限地球危机